Guide to the Time Inc. Administration, Human Resources and Personnel Records 1939-1994 (bulk 1968-1985) MS 3009-RG 17
New-York Historical Society
- Series III: Personnel: Vice President and Director: Robert M. Steed Files, 1939-1985 (bulk 1968-1985); 172394; 24 Linear feet in 24 record cartons
  - Subseries III.A: General Office Files, 1945-1984 (bulk 1968-1984); 172395; 11.8 Linear feet in 12 record cartons
    - Pregnancy Discrimination Act [RESTRICTED], 189219 (Offsite-box R6)
    - The President's Executive Exchange Program for Business Executives, 172696 (Offsite-box 637, Folder 22)
    - Privacy, 172697 (Offsite-box 637)
    - Privacy [RESTRICTED], 189220 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Probationary period concept, 172698 (Offsite-box 637, Folder 24)
    - Productivity, 172699 (Offsite-box 637, Folder 25)
    - Profit sharing, 172722 (Offsite-box 637)
    - Profit sharing [RESTRICTED], 189221 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Profit-sharing: 1979-80, 172724 (Offsite-box 637)
    - Profit-sharing: 1979-80 [RESTRICTED], 189222 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Profit-sharing historical data, 172721 (Offsite-box 637, Folder 29)
    - Profit-sharing offset, 172723 (Offsite-box 637, Folder 30)
    - Promotables list, 172700 (Offsite-box 637, Folder 31)
    - Public speaking program, 172701 (Offsite-box 637, Folder 32)
    - Record retention, 172702 (Offsite-box 637)
    - Record retention [RESTRICTED], 189223 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Recruitment, 172703 (Offsite-box 637, Folder 34-35)
    - Resumes - Samples, 172704 (Offsite-box 637, Folder 36)
    - Retirement: Counselling, 172726 (Offsite-box 637, Folder 37)
    - Retirement: Directory, 172727 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 1)
    - Retirement: Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation, 172728 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 2)
    - Retirement: Study, 172729 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 3)
    - Salary administration, 172705 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 4)
    - Salary studies, 172706 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 5)
    - Savings bonds - U.S., 172707 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 6)
    - Scholarships, 172708 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 7)
    - Secretaries, 172709 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 8)
    - Secretarial pool, 172710 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 9)
    - Selling Areas-Marketing, Inc. (SAMI), 172745 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 10)
    - Severance pay and re-hires, 172711 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 11)
    - Sexual harrassment, 172712 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 12)
    - Sick leave report, 172713 (Offsite-box 638)
    - Sick leave report [RESTRICTED], 189224 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Skills bank, 172714 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 14)
    - Social Security and Medicare, 172730 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 15)
    - Software publishing, 172731 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 16)
    - Special bonuses, 172732 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 17)
    - Speeches, 172733 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 18)
    - Staff development, 172734 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 19)
    - [Staff] lists, 172962 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 20)
    - Sterling Institute, 172735 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 21)
    - Stock bonus plan, 172736 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 22)
    - Stock investment plan, 172737 (Offsite-box 638)
    - Stock investment plan [RESTRICTED], 189225 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Stock option plan, 172738 (Offsite-box 638)
    - Stock option plan [RESTRICTED], 189226 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Stock options - Performance share plan, 172746 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 29)
    - Stock options - Miscellaneous, 172747 (Offsite-box 638)
    - Stock options - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 189227 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Stock performance plan, 172748 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 31)
    - Restricted stock plan, 172749 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 32)
    - Strategy development, 172750 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 33)
    - Stress, 172751 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 34)
    - Strike - Preparation for, 172752 (Offsite-box 638, Folder 35)
    - STV staff terminations [RESTRICTED], 172753 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Succession proposal, 172754 (Offsite-box 638-639)
    - Succession proposal [RESTRICTED], 189228 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Summer hiring, 172755 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 2)
    - Summer intern program, 172756 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 3)
    - Surveys - Personnel, 172757 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 4)
    - Syndication, 172758 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 5)
    - Synanon, 172759 (Offsite-box 639)
    - Synanon [RESTRICTED], 189229 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Takeover issues [RESTRICTED], 172760 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Talent Associates [RESTRICTED], 172761 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Targeted jobs tax credit, 172762 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 7)
    - Tax Act - 1982, 172763 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 8)
    - Tax deductible savings - Employee, 172764 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 9)
    - Tax Reduction Act Stock Ownership Plan (TRASOP), 172765 (Offsite-box 639)
    - Tax Reduction Act Stock Ownership Plan (TRASOP) [RESTRICTED], 189230 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Teletext, 172766 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 11)
    - Terminations: Economy, 172768 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 12)
    - Terminations: Miscellaneous, 172769 (Offsite-box 639)
    - Terminations: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 189231 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Time Inc.: Annual reports: 1984, 172771 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 14)
    - Time Inc.: "Comers" memo, 172772 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 15)
    - Time Inc.: Controls study, 172773 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 16)
    - Time Inc.: Distributions services, 172774 (Offsite-box 639)
    - Time Inc.: Distributions services [RESTRICTED], 189232 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Time Inc.: Organization, 172775 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 19)
    - Time Inc.: [1979-1983 Plan], 172776 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 20)
    - Time Inc.: 1980 Plan, 172777 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 21)
    - Time Inc.: Prospectus and proxy statements, 172778 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 22-23)
    - Time Inc.: Publicity, 172793 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 24)
    - Time Inc.: Reorganization, 172794 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 25)
    - Time Inc.: Scholars, 172795 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 26)
    - Time Inc.: Telephone marketing, 172796 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 27)
    - Time Inc.: Miscellaneous, 172797 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 28)
      Includes employee lists, subsidiary lists, various policies, and the trademark use manual.
    - Time-Life Books, 172800 (Offsite-box 639)
    - Time-Life Books [RESTRICTED], 189233 (Offsite-box R6)
    - Time-Life libraries, 172801 (Offsite-box 639)
    - Time-Life libraries [RESTRICTED], 189234 (Offsite-box R6)
    - TPF&C [Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby]: Pension Task Force material, 172803 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 31-32)
    - TPF&C [Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby]: Benefits: "I'm in Charge", 172804 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 33)
    - TPF&C [Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby]: Compensation data bank result, 172805 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 34)
    - Training, 172806 (Offsite-box 639, Folder 35)
    - Transfers, 172807 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 1)
    - Transit strike, 172808 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 2)
    - Tri-Starr [RESTRICTED], 172809 (Offsite-box R6)
    - TVIS, 172810 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 3)
    - Unemployment compensation, 172811 (Offsite-box 640)
    - Unemployment compensation [RESTRICTED], 189235 (Offsite-box R6)
    - United student aid - USAF [United Student Aid Fund] program, 172812 (Offsite-box 640)
    - United student aid - USAF [United Student Aid Fund] program [RESTRICTED], 189236 (Offsite-box R7)
    - [U.S. and international advertising sales and marketing services: Home addresses], 172813 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 6)
    - Utah State University conference, 172958 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 7)
    - Vacations, 172814 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 8-9)
      Includes informal application of comp time survey.
    - Veterans, 172815 (Offsite-box 640)
    - Veterans [RESTRICTED], 189237 (Offsite-box R7)
    - Video display terminals, 172816 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 11)
    - Video Group: Human resources conference, 172818 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 12-14)
    - Video Group: Human resources, 172819 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 15)
    - Video Group: LaQuinta meeting: November 1983, 172820 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 16)
    - Video Group: Human resources working group, 172821 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 17)
    - Vietnamese employees, 172822 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 18)
    - Visas, 172823 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 19)
    - Voluntary separation allowance, 172824 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 20)
    - Volunteer fund, 172825 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 21)
    - Voting, 172826 (Offsite-box 640)
    - Voting [RESTRICTED], 189238 (Offsite-box R7)
    - Wage guidelines, 172827 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 23-24)
    - Wage payment law, 172828 (Offsite-box 640)
    - Wage payment law [RESTRICTED], 189239 (Offsite-box R7)
    - WANG, 172869 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 26)
      Materials on using the Human Resources computer operating system.
    - Washington problems [RESTRICTED], 172961 (Offsite-box R7)
    - Washington Star [RESTRICTED], 172870 (Offsite-box R7)
    - White House fellows, 172871 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 27)
    - Wire room, 172872 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 28)
    - Women - Reference, 172873 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 29)
    - Women - Human Rights Commission: Reports (to), 172874 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 30)
    - Women - Human Rights Commission: Complaint and agreement, 172875 (Offsite-box 640)
    - Women - Human Rights Commission: Complaint and agreement [RESTRICTED], 189240 (Offsite-box R7)
    - Women's magazine, 172876 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 32)
    - Work week, 172877 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 33-34)
    - Workmen's compensation, 172878 (Offsite-box 640)
    - Workmen's compensation [RESTRICTED], 189241 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 6)
    - Writers, 172879 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 36)
      Includes policies and statistics on writers and reporters from 1949 to 1974.
    - Xerox - Learning systems, 172880 (Offsite-box 640)
    - Xerox - Learning systems [RESTRICTED], 189242 (Offsite-box R7)
    - Yankelovich questionnaire, 172881 (Offsite-box 640, Folder 38)
      Includes materials to create a survey to determine staff opinion on Time Inc.
  - Subseries III.B: Benefits, 1974-1984; 173030; 1.7 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    The Benefits files include correspondence and memoranda related to benefits plans, and drafts of and finalized benefits plans for Time Inc. employees.
    - Annuity and profit sharing, 173031 (Offsite-box 641, Folder 1-3)
    - Annuity and profit sharing [RESTRICTED], 190725 (Offsite-box R8)
    - Early retirement program, 173034 (Offsite-box 641)
    - Early retirement program [RESTRICTED], 189243 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 8)
    - ERIC [The ERISA Industry Committee], 173032 (Offsite-box 641, Folder 5)
    - ERISA [Employee Retirement Income Security Act], 173033 (Offsite-box 641, Folder 6-9)
    - Excess benefit plan, 173035 (Offsite-box 641, Folder 10)
    - Flexible benefits, 173036 (Offsite-box 641, Folder 11-12)
    - PAYSOP, 173037 (Offsite-box 641)
    - PAYSOP [RESTRICTED], 189244 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 9)
    - Profit-sharing savings plan, 173038 (Offsite-box 641)
    - Profit-sharing savings plan [RESTRICTED], 189245 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 10)
    - Pension plan, 173039 (Offsite-box 641-642)
    - Pension plan [RESTRICTED], 189246 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 11-14)
    - Retirement: Lump sum, 173040 (Offsite-box 642)
    - Retirement: Lump sum [RESTRICTED], 189247 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 15)
    - Retirement: Mandatory, 173041 (Offsite-box 642)
    - Retirement: Mandatory [RESTRICTED], 189248 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 16)
    - Retirement: Programs, 173042 (Offsite-box 642, Folder 5)
  - Subseries III.C: Human Resources Staff, approximately 1984; 172957; 0.5 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Organized alphabetically by last name.
    Human Resources Staff includes correspondence and memoranda between Robert Steed and his staff regarding their projects and assignments.
    - Bijur, Priscilla, 173043 (Offsite-box 642, Folder 6)
    - Clarke, Fred, 173044 (Offsite-box 642, Folder 7)
    - Clarke, Fred [RESTRICTED], 189249 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 17)
    - Faye, Toni, 173045 (Offsite-box 642, Folder 8)
    - Hiland, Bruce, 173046 (Offsite-box 642, Folder 9)
    - Kasofsky/Wilkinson, 173047 (Offsite-box 642, Folder 10)
    - Kohler, Eleanor, 173048 (Offsite-box 642, Folder 11)
    - Raley, Deane, 173049 (Offsite-box 642, Folder 12)
    - Ryden, Katherine, 173050 (Offsite-box 642, Folder 13)
  - Subseries III.D: International, 1976-1985; 172868; 1.4 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    International contains correspondence between Robert Steed in the corporate personnel office and staff from the international Time Inc. offices. The records also include directories, personnel office policies, and personnel statistics.
    Organized alphabetically with general files at the front.
    - General: Allowances, 172883 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 1)
    - General: Benefits, 172884 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 2)
    - General: Cost of living, 172885 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 3)
    - General: Directory, 172886 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 4)
    - General: Employee plans and benefits, 172887 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 5)
    - General: Headcount, 172888 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 6)
    - General: National Foreign Trade Council, 172889 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 7)
    - General: Raise review, 172890 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 8)
    - General: Renumeration, 172891 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 9)
    - General: Tax equalization, 172892 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 10)
    - General: Time Life: Europe, 172893 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 11)
    - General: Miscellaneous, 172894 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 12)
    - Australia, 172895 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 13)
    - Canada, 172896 (Offsite-box 643)
    - Canada [RESTRICTED], 189250 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 18)
    - France, 172897 (Offsite-box 643)
    - France [RESTRICTED], 189251 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 19)
    - Great Britain: General, 172898 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 16-17)
    - Great Britain: National Union of Journalists, 172899 (Offsite-box 643)
    - Great Britain: National Union of Journalists [RESTRICTED], 189252 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 20)
    - Germany, 172914 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 21)
    - Italy, 172915 (Offsite-box 643, Folder 22)
    - Japan, 172916 (Offsite-box 643-644)
    - Mexico, 172917 (Offsite-box 644, Folder 2)
    - Netherlands, 172918 (Offsite-box 644)
    - Netherlands [RESTRICTED], 189253 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 21)
    - Philippines, 172919 (Offsite-box 644, Folder 4)
  - Subseries III.E: Situations [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2058], 1975-1983; 172938; 0.5 Linear feet in 1 record carton (Offsite-box 645)
    Situations includes files on various performance, health or other issues with Time Inc. staff requiring the Personnel office's involvement.
  - Subseries III.F: Subsidiaries, 1974-1985; 172920; 3 Linear feet in 5 record cartons
    Organized alphabetically by company name with general files in the front.
    Subsidiaries contains correspondence between Robert Steed in the corporate personnel office and staff from the subsidiary companies owned by Time Inc. The records include discussion on how to adjust, incorporate or combine the subsidiary's original policies and benefits with Time Inc.'s; reports on benefits, compensation, and personnel statistics; and employee handbooks.
    - General, 172922 (Offsite-box 644, Folder 5)
    - General: List of, 172923 (Offsite-box 644, Folder 6)
    - General: Moving policy, 172924 (Offsite-box 644, Folder 7)
    - ATC [American Television and Communications Corporation], 172925 (Offsite-box 644)
    - ATC [American Television and Communications Corporation] [RESTRICTED], 189254 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 22)
    - Books Division, 172926 (Offsite-box 644)
    - Books Division [RESTRICTED], 189255 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 23)
    - Book-of-the-Month, 172927 (Offsite-box 644, Folder 17)
    - Forest Products, 172928 (Offsite-box 644, Folder 18)
    - Forest Products [RESTRICTED], 187254 (Offsite-box 645)
    - Georgia Kraft, 172929 (Offsite-box 644, Folder 19)
    - Home Box Office [HBO], 172930 (Offsite-box 644, 650)
    - Home Box Office [HBO] [RESTRICTED], 189256 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 24)
    - Inland Container, 172931 (Offsite-box 650)
    - Inland Container [RESTRICTED], 189257 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 25)
    - Little, Brown & Company, 172932 (Offsite-box 650, Folder 7)
    - Manhattan Cable Television, 172933 (Offsite-box 650)
    - Manhattan Cable Television [RESTRICTED], 189258 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 26)
    - Pioneer Press, 172934 (Offsite-box 650)
    - Pioneer Press [RESTRICTED], 189259 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 27)
    - Temple-Eastex, 172935 (Offsite-box 650, Folder 12-16)
    - Temple-Eastex [RESTRICTED], 187273 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 28)
    - Time-Life Films, 172936 (Offsite-box 650-651)
    - Time-Life Films [RESTRICTED], 189260 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 29-30)
    - Washington Star, 172937 (Offsite-box 651)
    - Washington Star [RESTRICTED], 189261 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 31-33)
  - Subseries III.G. Union Relations, 1939-1983; 172941; 4.1 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
    Union Relations contains the Personnel office's research and work on job classifications, and Time Inc.'s interactions and negotiations with the Newspaper Guild of New York. Besides Steed's records, there are records from Louis Gratz in the Labor Relations office, which was not part of Personnel. These records are comingled with Steed's records, and Steed might have inherited them. The records include meeting minutes and a salary study from the Continuing Classification Committee, copies of union contracts from other news organizations along with other research dating back to 1939, Time Inc. job descriptions, and Time Inc.'s union contracts.
    - Classifications: Category Review: General: 1974-1975, 180540 (Offsite-box 651, Folder 5-12)
    - Classifications: Categories: Miscellaneous Memoranda, 187222 (Offsite-box 651, Folder 13)
    - Classifications: Category Review: Editorial: 1970, 180541 (Offsite-box 651, Folder 14)
    - Classifications: Categories: Editorial Job Descriptions: 1964, 180542 (Offsite-box 651, Folder 15)
    - Classifications: Categories: Meetings, 180543 (Offsite-box 651, Folder 16-17)
    - Classifications: Category Lists, 180544 (Offsite-box 651, Folder 18-19)
    - Classifications: Category List Head Count Study: 1953-1969, 180545 (Offsite-box 652, Folder 1-2)
    - Classifications: Continuing Classification Committee, 180546 (Offsite-box 652, Folder 3-10)
    - Classifications: Copy Desk, 180547 (Offsite-box 652, Folder 11)
    - Classifications: Job Descriptions, 180548 (Offsite-box 652-653)
    - Classifications: Negotiations: 1971, 180549 (Offsite-box 653, Folder 3)
    - Classifications: Reclassifications, 180550 (Offsite-box 653, Folder 4)
    - Contracts: General: Provisions, 180557 (Offsite-box 653, Folder 5)
    - Contracts: General: Rights and Controls, 180558 (Offsite-box 653, Folder 6)
    - Contracts: Newspapers and Wire Services, 180552 (Offsite-box 653, Folder 7)
    - Contracts: Other Companies: Misc., 180553 (Offsite-box 653, Folder 8-9)
    - Contracts: Other Companies: Duration and Renewal, 187227 (Offsite-box 653, Folder 10)
    - Contracts: Other Companies: Other Magazines, 187228 (Offsite-box 653, Folder 11)
    - Contracts: Other Companies: Other Publishers: Comparison Clauses, 187229 (Offsite-box 653, Folder 12-13)
    - Contracts: Other Companies: Newsweek, 180560 (Offsite-box 653)
    - Contracts: Other Companies: Newsweek [RESTRICTED], 189262 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 34)
    - Contracts: Other Companies: New York Daily News, 180561 (Offsite-box 653, Folder 20-22)
    - Contracts: Other Companies: New York Post, 180562 (Offsite-box 653, Folder 23-25)
    - Contracts: Other Companies: New York Times, 180563 (Offsite-box 654, Folder 1-14)
    - Contracts: Press Wireless, Inc., 180565 (Offsite-box 654, Folder 15)
    - Contracts: Publishers Association and Printing Pressmen's Union, 180555 (Offsite-box 654, Folder 16)
    - Contracts: Saturday Review, 180559 (Offsite-box 654, Folder 17)
    - Contracts: Standard and Poors, 180556 (Offsite-box 654, Folder 18)
    - Newspapers: General, 180564 (Offsite-box 654, Folder 19)
    - Newspapers: Clippings, 180566 (Offsite-box 654, Folder 20)
    - Newspapers: Delivery Unions, 180567 (Offsite-box 654, Folder 21)
    - Newspapers: New York: Settlements, 180568 (Offsite-box 654, Folder 22)
    - Newspapers: New York: Strike: 1963, 180569 (Offsite-box 654, Folder 23-24)
    - Newspapers: Outside New York: Strike Reports, 180570 (Offsite-box 655, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Guild of New York: Time Inc. Negotiations and Contracts: 1966-1972, 1983, 180539 (Offsite-box 655)
    - Newspaper Guild of New York: Time Inc. Negotiations and Contracts: 1966-1972, 1983 [RESTRICTED], 189263 (Offsite-box R7, Folder 35-36)
- Series IV: Human Resources: Vice President: John R. Bingle Files, 1974-1985; 172341; 2.1 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  The arrangement of this series is based on the original arrangement of office files grouped chronologically by year.
  These files were found housed together and the primary correspondent is John "Jay" R. Bingle, VP of Human Resources. His files include correspondence, memoranda, and reports regarding Time Inc. benefits, compensation, and policies.
  - 1977: Personnel and Compensation Committee, 172345 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 1)
  - 1983: Group insurance, 172346 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 2)
  - 1983-1984: Benefit plan amendments, 172347 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 3-4)
  - 1983-1985: Pisces Project Team, 187046 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 5)
  - 1984: Alfred P. Sloan Fellow Program: M.I.T., 172348 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 6)
  - 1984: Cinemax contracts [RESTRICTED], 172349 (Offsite-box R6)
  - 1984: Cost containment, 172350 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 7)
  - 1984: Excess benefits contributions, 172351 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 8)
  - 1984: Hewitt Associates Administrative Services Proposal, 172354 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 9)
  - 1984: Management development programs, 172355 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 10)
  - 1984: Pensions: General, 172357 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 11)
  - 1984: Pensions: Time Employees' Pension Plan, 172358 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 12)
  - 1984: Pensions: Executive summary: Funding study, 172359 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 13)
  - 1984: Retirement Income Plan: Book-of-the-Month Club, 187047 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 14)
  - 1984: The School of Management and Strategic Studies, 172360 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 15)
  - 1984: Sigma Financial, 172361 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 16)
  - 1984: Stock options, 172987 (Offsite-box 628, Folder 17-18)
  - 1984: Stock option plans, 172988 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 1)
  - 1984: TPF&C, 172362 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 2-3)
  - 1985: ACME, 172364 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 4)
  - 1985: AACSB, 172365 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 5)
  - 1985: BOMC [Book-of-the-Month Club] task force, 172366 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 6)
  - 1985: Compensation strategy: Books Group, 172367 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 7)
  - 1985: Development, 172368 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 8)
  - 1985: Direct reports-objectives, 172369 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 9)
  - 1985: Employee rights, 172370 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 10)
  - 1985: Human resources budget, 172344 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 11-13)
  - 1985: [Materials prepared for discussion of leveraged ESOPs], 172371 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 14)
  - 1985: SPC acquisition, 172372 (Offsite-box 629, Folder 15)